Huth, Geoffrey A.; Papers mss137
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Biographical Records, 1960; 1962; 1964-2006; 1; 9 cubic ft.
  - Work, 1978; 1987-2006; 1.5; 2.50 cubic ft.
    - State Education Department Leadership Academy, 2004-2005 (Box 4 (1-Biographical Records), Folder 4)
    - Swensen's Rivergate Mall, Goodlettsville, Tennessee, 1979 (Box 4 (1-Biographical Records), Folder 5)
    - World Trade Center Documentation Task Force, 2003 (Box 4 (1-Biographical Records), Folder 6)
    - New York State Archives Work Poster, 1992 (Box 5 (1-Biographical Records), Folder 1)
    - Two Original Illustrations from Venus, Undated (Box 5 (1-Biographical Records), Item 2)
      1. one from "On the Wall" 2. one Illustrating "The Travels of Coglioni".
    - Copies of a Work Poster designed by Geof Huth, Undated (Box 5 (1-Biographical Records), Item 3)
- Writing and Art, 1976-2006; 2; 3.5 cubic ft. + 2 GB
  This series consists of paper and electronic manuscripts of all the types of artistic works produced by Geof Huth (poetry, fiction, essays, aphorisms, visual poems, dramatic works, comics, digital poems, and others).
  - Writing and Art, 1976-2006; 2.1; 3.5 cubic ft.
    Consists of drafts and final versions of paper manuscripts of writing and art projects organized by subcategory: Aphorisms, Comics, Conceptual Texts, Dictionaries, Dramatic Works, Essays, Fiction, Light Verse, Poems, Pwoermds, Visual Art, and Visual Poems. Includes oversized material stored separately.
    Arranged alphabetically by type of work and alphabetically by title thereunder.
    - Aphorisms, Cages in Search of a Bird, Undated (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 1)
    - Aphorisms, thingk wOeird, ca. 1995 (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 2)
    - Comics, The Comics Gallery, Undated (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 3)
    - Comics, Mister Splinter, Undated (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 4)
    - Conceptual Concepts-Drafts, Various Conceptual Texts, 1989 (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 5)
    - Dictionaries, Dictionary of Forgotten Meaning, 1994 (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 6)
    - Dictionaries, Familiar Words, Final, pages 1-170, 1996 (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 7)
    - Dictionaries, Familiar Words, Final, pages 171-306, 1996 (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 8)
    - Dictionaries, Familiar Words, Print Copy, pages 1-170, 1996 (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 9)
    - Dictionaries, Familiar Words, Print Copy, pages 171-306, 1996 (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 10)
    - Dictionaries-Drafts, Familiar Words: How We Speak Alone Together, 1994 September (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 11)
    - Dictionaries-Drafts, Familiar Words, 2 October 2004 (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 12)
    - Dictionaries-Drafts, Familiar Words: How We Speak Alone Together, Bibliography, Undated (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 13)
    - Dictionaries-Drafts, Familiar Words, Final Draft, with Final Edits, 1996 November (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 14-15)
    - Dictionaries-Drafts, The Futuramanary, 4 May 1999 (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 16)
    - Dictionaries-Drafts, The Futuramanary, 2000 (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 17)
    - Dictionaries, A Historical Dictionary of Verbo-Visual Art and Related Forms, HDVVA, ca. 1990 (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 18)
    - Dictionaries, Historical Dictionary of Visual Poetry and Related Terms, 16 July 2001 (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 19)
    - Dictionaries, Historical Dictionary of Visual Poetry and Related Terms, 8 August 2001 (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 20)
    - Dictionaries, Historical Dictionary of Visual Poetry and Related Terms, 27 August 2001 (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 21)
    - Dictionaries, The Huthicon, Notes, 1997; 2003 (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 22)
    - Dictionaries, The Huthicon, 13 June 1998 (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 23)
    - Dictionaries-Drafts, The Huthicon, 2000-2001 (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 24)
    - Dictionaries-Drafts, Lexicon of Governmental Records Services, 1994 (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 25)
    - Dictionaries-Drafts, Literary Dictionary of the Becoming Tongue, 1994 (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 26)
    - Dictionaries-Drafts, Neologisms, 1984 (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 27)
    - Dictionaries-Drafts, Neologisms of Geof Huth, ca. 1987 (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 28)
    - Dictionaries-Drafts, The Nonciary, ca. 1988 (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 29)
    - Dictionaries-Drafts, The Nonciary, 10 September 1994 (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 30)
    - Dictionaries, A Sampling from Familiar Words, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 31)
    - Dictionaries-Drafts, The Simpsonary, 5 June 1998; 26 July 1998 (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 32)
    - Dictionaries-Drafts, The Simpsonary, 5 September 1998 (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 33)
    - Dictionaries-Drafts, The Simpsonary, pages 1-400, 1998 (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 34)
    - Dictionaries-Drafts, The Simpsonary, pages 401-800, 23 July 2000 (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 35)
    - Dictionaries-Drafts, The Simpsonary, pages 1-380, 9 May 1999 (Box 1 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 36)
    - Dictionaries-Drafts, The Simpsonary, pages 381-700, plus additions, 9 May 1999 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 1)
    - Dictionaries-Drafts, The Simpsonary, 23 July 2000 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 2)
    - Dictionaries, Webster's Roget's Dictionary of Forgotten Meaning, ca. 1993 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 3)
    - Dramatic Pieces, Short Dramatic Pieces, Undated (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 4)
    - Dramatic Works, Chester's Progress, Undated (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 5)
    - Dramatic Works, The Invention of the World, Undated (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 6)
    - Essays, &2: an/thology of pwoermds, Drafts, 2003-2004 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 7)
    - Essays, &2: an/thology of pwoermds, Notes, 2004 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 8)
    - Essays-Drafts, Afterwhich: Maureen Huth's Bolivian Diary, 28 October 1973-23 December 1973, 2001 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 9)
    - Essays, Afterwhich: Maureen Huth's Bolivian Diary, 28 October 1973-23 December 1973, 2001 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 10)
    - Essays, The Anti-Manifesto to Manifesto, 1989 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 11)
    - Essays, Bob Grumman Reviews Your Life, 1996 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 12)
    - Essays, Concrete Poetry Essay, ca. 1984 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 13)
    - Essays, A Critique of Pure Trivia: Limericks, Totem Symbols, and Other Decorations, Undated (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 14)
    - Essays, Doing Time: In Somalia, Undated (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 15)
    - Essays, Encyclopedia of Local History, 1999 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 16)
    - Essays-Drafts, Endwords, 1992 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 17)
    - Essays, The First Picture Show, 2002 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 18)
    - Essays-Drafts, Huth's Familial Quotations, 1996 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 19)
    - Essays-Drafts, I Can't (Help But) Read This, 2003 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 20)
    - Essays, I Can't (Help But) Read This, 2003 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 21)
    - Essays, The Identity of the Text, 1985; 1990 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 22)
    - Essays-Drafts, The Identity of the Text, 1985 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 23)
    - Essays, The Illustration of Art, Undated (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 24)
    - Essays, Inter Intermedia All is What We Need, Undated (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 25)
    - Essays, Intolerance II, Undated (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 26)
    - Essays-Drafts, Is, Mailart, This, Mailart, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 27)
    - Essays-Drafts, Lou Reed: Inverse, Reverse, Perverse, Undated (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 28)
    - Essays, (My)self, 1987 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 29)
    - Essays-Drafts, My Right Foot: A Pedestrian Journal of a Plague Year, 2002 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 30)
    - Essays, Of Poetry and Speech and Print, 1995 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 31)
    - Essays, Of Ten, He Writes Frequently, 1 February 1992 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 32)
    - Essays, Oporto, Portugal, 1966-1967 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 33)
    - Essays, Reflections on the Art Strike, 1990-1993 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 34)
    - Essays, Remembering Family, Word Folklore History Artifact Archives, (numbered pdqb 88, but not released), 2002 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 35)
    - Essays, School Essays, Master of Arts, American History, 1989-1991 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 36)
    - Essays, School Essays, Master of Arts, English, 1984-1985 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 37)
    - Essays, School Papers, Master of Library Science, 1988-1989 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 38)
    - Essays, School Papers, Vanderbilt University, 1978 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 39)
    - Essays, Small Attempts, Undated (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 40)
    - Essays, Some Neglected Printing Processes for the Nocturnal Press, 1991 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 41)
    - Essays, Strike or Lockout, The Printers and Newspaper Publishers of Albany, New York, 1928-1929, ca. 1992 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 42)
    - Essays-Drafts, Textuactualities, Undated (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 43)
    - Essays, Through the Land of the Sinking Sun, Undated (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 44)
    - Essays, The Way Which Grassblades Burst through the Sidewalk, Undated (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 45)
    - Essays, Vanderbilt University Graffiti, 1980-1981 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 46)
    - Essays-Drafts, What is Aporia?, 1985; 1990 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 47)
    - Essays, What is Aporia?, 1990 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 48)
    - Essays-Drafts, What Pauline Tends Toward, 1987 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 49)
    - Essays-Introductions, With Tents, There are Fields, 1989 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 50)
    - Essays, Word Processing, 1986 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 51)
    - Essays, Word Processing with AppleWorks, 1986 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 52)
    - Essays, Wordscapes and Viewsheds: The Minimalist Poetry of LeRoy Gorman, 2002 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 53)
    - Fiction, After that, she didn't, using the Huthery typeface, Undated (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 54)
    - Fiction-Drafts, The Book of Beings, 1982; 1986 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 55)
    - Fiction-Drafts, Dint, 1999-2001 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 56)
    - Fiction, The Empty Sleeve, 1979 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 57)
    - Fiction-Drafts, Figured from Speech, ca. 1992 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 58)
    - Fiction, The Going of a Boy through the Night, Undated (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 59)
    - Fiction-Drafts, The Gunslinger, the West, and the Last Great Freedom Ride into the Desert, ca. 1983 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 60)
    - Fiction, Her Age It Was Red and Her Hair Was 16, Undated (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 61)
    - Fiction, Her Age It Was Red and Her Hair Was 16, Undated (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 62)
    - Fiction, Her Body Moves With Malice, Undated (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 63)
    - Fiction-Drafts, In the Mountains, the Various Acts of Faith, Undated (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 64)
    - Fiction, In the Mountain, the Various Acts of Faith, Undated (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 65)
    - Fiction, Killing Women: How a Ray Carver Story is Written, ca. 1984 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 66)
    - Fiction, The Last Word/The Last Work of Samuel Beckett, Undated (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 67)
    - Fiction, The Man Without Arms, with note by V.S. Pritchett, Undated (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 68)
    - Fiction-Drafts, Of All These Friends and Lovers, with notes by V.S. Pritchett, Undated (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 69)
    - Fiction, Of All These Friends and Lovers, Undated (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 70)
    - Fiction, The Purple Princess, 1990 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 71)
    - Fiction-Drafts, Robin Smythe, ca. 1983 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 72)
    - Fiction, The Search Against the Pumpkintree, Undated (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 73)
    - Fiction, Short Short Stories, Undated (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 74)
    - Fiction, The Shortest Finnegans Wake, Undated (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 75)
    - Fiction-Drafts, Signs of Oconomowoc, Wisconsin, ca. 1980-1986 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 76)
    - Fiction, The Times of the Lives of Sammy the Grapefruit-Grafter, with notes by V.S. Pritchett, Undated (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 77)
    - Fiction, The Travels of Coglioni, Undated (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 78)
    - Fiction, Whenever She Reaches Somewhere, 1987 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 79)
    - Font Design, Font Design, 1995-2000 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 80)
    - Font Design, Spidertangle Font Contributions @ q H 2, Undated (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 81)
    - Haikai-Drafts, Haibun, 2002 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 82)
    - Haikai-Drafts, Haiga, 2002 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 83)
    - Haikai-Drafts, Haiku, 1979 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 84)
    - Light Verse, Animal Alphabet, 1980 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 85)
    - Light Verse-Drafts, Apples, Pears, Crabapples, Quinces, and Medlars, Poems for Eating, 1978-1984 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 86)
    - Light Verse-Drafts, Birthday Poems, Erin Huth, 2000-2002 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 87)
    - Light Verse-Drafts, Birthday Poems, Timothy Huth, 2000 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 88)
    - Light Verse, Box of Books, 1981-1986 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 89)
    - Light Verse, Clerihews, ca. 1985 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 90)
    - Light Verse, This Little Kitty, Anniversary Poem to Nancy Huth, 2002 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 91)
    - Light Verse, Uncollected Light Verse, 1991-1992 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 92)
    - Light Verse-Drafts, Vulgar Satires, 1983 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 93)
    - Logo Design-Drafts, Spidertangle Logos, 2002 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 94)
    - Logo Design, Spidertangle Logos, 2002 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 95)
    - Poems-Drafts, Alphapoems, 1986; 1987; 2001 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 96)
    - Poetry, The Birth of the Island of Surtsey, 1963, Final Thesis Version, 1986 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 97)
    - Poetry, The Birth of the Island of Surtsey, 1963, 1985 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 98)
    - Poetry-Drafts, The Birth of the Island of Surtsey, 1963, Undated (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 99)
    - Poetry-Drafts, The Birth of the Island of Surtsey, 1963, 1986 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 100)
    - Poetry-Drafts, The Birth of the Island of Surtsey, 1963, 1987 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 101)
    - Poetry, a book of poems so small I cannot taste them, 2005 (Box 2 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 102)
    - Poetry-Drafts, Carl, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 1)
    - Poetry-Drafts, Carmen 365, 1983-1986 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 2)
    - Poetry-Drafts, Clay Todd, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 3)
    - Poems-Drafts, Couplet Poems, 1989 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 4)
    - Poems-Drafts, A Disease of Carcass Awaiting, 1990; 1992 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 5)
    - Poetry-Drafts, Epigrammar, 1984-1985 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 6)
    - Poetry-Drafts, Epithalamia, 2001 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 7)
    - Poems-Drafts, Eucalyptus Tea in the Shade, ca. 1983 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 8)
    - Poetry-Drafts, Filbert, 1989 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 9)
    - Poetry-Drafts, Gingerbread Doom, 1984 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 10)
    - Poetry-Drafts, He Saw the Ocean as a Fish, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 11)
    - Poetry-Drafts, Jacquelynne Elizabeth-Anne, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 12)
    - Poetry-Drafts, Lacunae, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 13)
    - Poems-Drafts, Legend, 1986-1995 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 14)
    - Poems-Drafts, Lines Upon, 1986 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 15)
    - Poems-Drafts, The Lost Poems, 1985 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 16)
    - Poetry-Drafts, The Northern Woods, 1984 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 17)
    - Poetry-Drafts, One Million Footnotes, 2004 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 18)
    - Poetry-Drafts, Paralipomena, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 19)
    - Poetry-Drafts, Pebbleslight, 1983-2002 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 20)
    - Poems, Squeezing, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 21)
    - Poems-Drafts, A Topographical Description and Admeasurement of the YLAND of Barbados in the West INDYAES with the Mrs. Names of Seuerall plantcons, ca. 1984 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 22)
    - Poems, Uncollected Poems, 1992 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 23)
    - Poetry-Drafts, Zuzu's Petals, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 24)
    - Pwoermds, forked lake, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 25)
    - Pwoermds-Drafts, forked lake, 2001 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 26)
    - Pwoermds, Uncollected Pwoermds, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 27)
    - Pwoermds, wreadings, 1987 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 28)
    - Pwoermds-Drafts, wreadings, 1986-1987 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 29)
    - Visual Art, Elephant Head, Drawing from Ghana, ca. 1976 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 30)
    - Visual Art, Xerographic Study of a Dead Squirrel, ca. 1980 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 31)
    - Visual Art, Xerographic Studies of Fingernails, ca. 1990 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 32)
    - Visual Poems, Adam's gift, 1990-1991 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 33)
    - Visual Poems-Drafts, Analphabet, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 34)
    - Visual Poetry, Analphabet, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 35)
    - Visual Poetry-Drafts, Address to Sender, 1986 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 36)
    - Visual-Poetry-Drafts, Algebraic Poems, 2002 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 37)
    - Visual Poetry-Drafts, Amoeba Poema, 1986-1987 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 38)
    - Visual Poems-Drafts, Ass-Paint Portraiture, 1988; 1990 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 39)
    - Visual Poetry-Drafts, Bite the Wax Tadpole, 1979-1986 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 40)
    - Visual Poems, bo,ok of unLlo?db, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 41)
    - Visual Poems-Drafts, The Book of Cells, 2002 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 42)
    - Visual Poems-Drafts, Bowhowse, 2002 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 43)
    - Visual Poetry-Drafts, China-Ankh-Chain, 1986-1987 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 44)
    - Visual Poems, Colors of the Alphabet, 2005-2006 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 45)
    - Visual Poetry, Corpo Morto com Adagio, 15 May 2005 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 46)
    - Visual Poems, Dachau: Afterwards, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 47)
    - Visual Poetry, Dreams of the Fishwife, small maters, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 48)
    - Visual Poetry, Dreams of the Fishwife, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 49)
    - Visual Poetry, Disembodied Incarnate, ca. 1989 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 50)
    - Visual Poems-Drafts, egg, a flipbook, 1987 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 51)
    - Visual Poetry-Drafts, Europa Wand, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 52)
    - Visual Poems-Drafts, A Few Crayon Poems, 1986 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 53)
    - Visual Poetry-Drafts, A Fidgetbook, the fourth book of cells, another random collection of fidgetglyphs, second half of the book, 2003 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 54)
    - Visual Poetry-Drafts, The Field, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 55)
    - Visual Poetry-Drafts, forked tung stem, 2002-2003 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 56)
    - Visual Poetry-Drafts, A Fidgetbook: the Fourth Book of Cells, 2003 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 57)
    - Visual Poetry-Drafts, Found and Aleatoric Poems, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 58)
    - Visual Poems, ghostlight, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 59)
    - Visual Poetry-Drafts, ghostlight, 1987; 1990 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 60)
    - Visual Poetry-Drafts, Here Now Am I Now Am Here, 1979-1987 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 61)
    - Visual Poems-Drafts, Herma of Phthis, 1986 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 62)
    - Visual Poems-Drafts, Hierofidgetglyphs: The Third Book of Cells, 2003 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 63-64)
    - Visual Poems, Ight, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 65)
    - Visual Poems-Drafts, Immediart, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 66)
    - Visual Poems-Drafts, Interior Definitions, 1986 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 67)
    - Visual Poems, I'ts, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 68)
    - Visual Poems-Drafts, I'ts, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 69)
    - Visual Poems, Interior Definitions, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 70)
    - Visual Poems-Drafts, Interior Definitions, 1986-1988 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 71)
    - Visual Poems-Drafts, The Jester's Gestures, 1991; 2004 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 72)
    - Visual Poetry-Drafts, Klediments Grandma Quilted out of the Things of Her Home, 1987 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 73)
    - Visual Poems, Making Order Out of Chaos for Over 5 Years, ca. 1989 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 74)
    - Visual Poetry-Drafts, Memory, Loss, Discovery, 2002 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 75)
    - Visual Poems-Drafts, The Moonseamed Birch, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 76)
    - Visual Poems-Drafts, Naming the Parts, 1983-1986 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 77)
    - Visual Poems-Drafts, OCEAN/CEASE/EASES/ASEAS/NESSS, 1986-1987 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 78)
    - Visual Poems-Drafts, Opal, Onyx, Obsidian, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 79)
    - Visual Poetry, The Past's Ricocheting Aeronautical Catechisms, 2004 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 80)
    - Visual Poems, Pebbleslight, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 81)
    - Visual Poems, Peristyle, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 82)
    - Visual Poems-Drafts, Peristyle, 1983-1987 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 83)
    - Visual Poems, poeyems, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 84)
    - Visual Poems, Punc; Tual, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 85)
    - Visual Poetry-Drafts, The Revolutions of the Perfect Circle, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 86)
    - Visual Poems-Drafts, The Second Book of Cells, 2002 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 87)
    - Visual Poems-Drafts, self seen, 2005 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 88)
    - Visual Poetry, seenside, 3 March 1995 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 89)
    - Visual Poetry, sno, 2005 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 90)
    - Visual Poems-Drafts, Signs, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 91)
    - Visual Poetry-Drafts, st.rl...t/m..nl...t, 1987 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 92)
    - Visual Poetry-Drafts, Submission to X-Ray #1, 1993 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 93)
    - Visual Poetry-Drafts, SYSTEMSYSTEMS, 1987-1988 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 94)
    - Visual Poetry-Drafts, These, Palimpsests, Undated (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 95)
    - Visual Poems-Drafts, Thelfbet, 2000 (Box 3 (2-Writing and Art), Folder 96)